Evil wants to be seen.
Watcher is a horror, mystery, thriller film directed by Chloe Okuno.
As a serial killer stalks the city, Julia — a young actress who just moved to town with her
husband — notices a mysterious stranger watching her from across the street.
Julia, played by Maika Monroe.
Francis, played by Karl Glusman.
Watcher, played by Burn Gorman.
Irina, played by Mãdãlina Anea.
Cristian, played by Daniel Nuta.
Flavia, played by Gabriela Butuc.
Watcher is a 2022 psychological thriller film written and directed by Chloe Okuno in her
feature directorial debut, based on an original screenplay by Zack Ford.
The film stars Maika Monroe, Karl Glusman, and Burn Gorman.
Watcher had its world premiere at the Sundance Film Festival on January
21, 2022, where it was nominated for the Grand Jury Prize.
The film was theatrically released in the United States on
June 3, 2022, to positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of husband wife relationship,
window, paranoia, language barrier, stalker.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.